(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-01T22:44:24.098244",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I'm Gigi Murin.
I used to be 14 years old in 8th grade, but now I'm not!
I'm a bit clumsy, crazy, and silly,
and I may not look it, but actually, I'm a member of Hololive English -Justice-.
That's true!
You can call me the Fister, because of my big, big power glove...
People don't really like that I call myself the Fister, and I don't really know why...
...literally called the Fister, because I fist people, you know? You know what I mean?
Today is the day of a very important Justice meeting,
but I... I accidentally overslept!
So I have to hurry up and make sure to look both ways
before crossing the road, and... go!
Gigi goes flying!
Ouch! Who is that? Why is it so weird?
Wow. Where am I?
A... beautiful 2D fantasy world?
I was supposed to get hit by a car,
and get Isekai'd...
Get hit by a car and it would be really cool... What the...
A horse?! That's not a truck!
That's dangerous! I could've died!
But phew... That grem sure knows how to drive!
Gremlin driver—
Ow... My body hurts...
I feel like I got run over by something, but I don't know what...
Oh. Is that a statue of a grem? Looks cool.
Wait a second... I know this! I've been Isekai'd!
What the freak? Gigi, you're hit too?
Justice cardboard?
Gigi, what's going on? Where are we?
What are you guys doing? Why are you cardboard?
Wow, CC looks so flat!
You f***ing b***h! How dare you do this to me! You b***h! This is your fault somehow! I don't know how you did this,
you little dumb b***h! Oh, you look terrible!
Well, let's go investigate around here.
Yeah, let's go. / Okay!
I'm on my way! Wait, guys! Wait for me! We can have an adventure together!
We can have an adventure together, and it'll be so fun! And...
Wait... Wait... What's going on?
Horses! Two of them!
Goodbye, leaving heartache of the past behind
There's no more turning back
Looking back, it's time
Moving down our own path
Evermore voyaging forward to make
this journey last...
Never spoken about in the light
Like a promise found riding the wind
Where a path begins spiraling outward and up
An inspiring tale begins
We who dare defy changing of times
As we follow unreachable dreams
Now it's here and right now that we're drawn to somehow
Deep inside a will to live that won't leave
With all this aching
Wandering near and far, touching lives just like ours
Lighting fires till I'm wasted away
One day, I'll recall these nights
Our relentless odyssey
Pressing onward, we never surrender
Toward the skies, we can rise again
I WAS HIT BY A TRUCK AND REINCARNATED AS THE PROTAGONIST IN A FANTASY WORLD BUT THEN A HORSE RAN ME OVER AND NOW ALL MY FRIENDS ARE CARDBOARD?
[Title: I WAS HIT BY A TRUCK AND REINCARNATED AS THE PROTAGONIST IN A FANTASY WORLD BUT THEN A HORSE RAN ME OVER AND NOW ALL MY FRIENDS ARE CARDBOARD?]
If anything else hits me, I don't think I'll survive much longer.
I really need to be more careful.
Thank goodness I'm still alive.
The winds whispered of your coming...
...and now, here you are.
Who are you?
I am the greatest wizard in all of Grem Kingdom.
Wizard Oji-chan.
Wizard Oji-chan?
Are you Wizard or Oji-chan?
Is that a name? What should I call you?
So many of Grem's warriors have fallen, one by one,
while we waited for your arrival...
Okay.
The wait was worth it!
You are far more powerful than I ever imagined a hero could be!
He's not responding to me.
He's probably an NPC. Is this a game?
NPC?!
ちょっと... ちょっと待ってください...
Wait... Wait a second...
Oh, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Wizard! Oji-chan!
I'm sorry, I didn't know you could talk!
You're the key.
Without you, your friend and this world are lost...
What? Lost? What are you talking about?
Gigi...
...the world is waiting...
He knows my name! That's me!
I'm the hero! I'm gonna save the world from being cardboard!
Huzzah!
What did you do to me?! It hurts! It hurts!
ちょっと... ちょっと...
Wait... Hold on...
What are you saying?
Huzzah!
Wow! I'm so cute and soft and fluffy now! Friends with you! Purchase next time they're in stock!
ちょっと... 痛い痛い... ごめん、もう一回... 日本語ちゃんとやるから...
Wait... that hurt... Sorry, one more time... I'll do the Japanese properly...
I don't understand!
Okay, okay, okay!
Is he gonna do it again? Whoa, he's really getting into this!
行け！行け！
Go! Go!
Squeak! Squeak squeak!
Not squeak, squeak! What's that?!
行くぞ！
Here I go!
I'm ready!
時空！時空包陣！
Time-space! Time-space sealing spell!
Do it!
Ugh...
Oh, wait! I can move now! What is...
What is this?
Hands? You did it! You've done it!
Oh my god, look how cute I am!
Aw, I've always been cute, but now... now it's even cuter! Now everyone can see how cute I...
Look at that fat tail! Look at that fat tail!
I can do everything!
I can't do that.
Watch this, guys. You've never seen this before.
Okay, okay... Wheee! Wheee! I can do everything.
Two in a row? Just kidding.
I have a world to save.
Look at that, everyone loves me!
Gigi Murin!
[Wizard grunting]
Is he...
Oh, I'm so dizzy... Oh, I'm so sorry.
What... what should I do to save everyone?
Oh, the world is spinning... Owie...
Before saving everyone, let's see if you can survive basic chores.
Basic cho-- I can do basic chores!
Let's start with...
Start with what?
What? What are we starting with?
Eagles! Go, eagles! Go!
Wait! What? What is he doing? What is he doing with the eagles?
Go, go, go, set on them!
Please wait! Wait! No! No!
The birds took him! I knew I could never trust a bird!
Hey you, Come here! Follow me!
A grem!
Um, I have to help my... my friends.
You're scared and lost... Not knowing what to do, right?
I'll show you how to save your friends. Follow me!
Oh, okay!
So small!
This place is weird.
This place is dark and it smells bad!
Hey it smells good!!!! Do exactly as I say if you want to save your friends!
Go to the Grem Kingdom and return with the One Ping, a Honkshoe, and a Straw Hat.
Why do you need them?
YOU DON'T GET TO ASK ME ANY QUESTIONS!!! NOW GO GIGI, GOOOOOO!!
Okay.
Woah!
So this is the Grem Kingdom?
It's so cool! There's so many grems!
Does this mean this entire kingdom is mine if I save it?
Woah, so many of you!
Oh, not all at once. No, no, no, no. What?
Oh, I can't hear you. Let's try this grem.
Lucky little grem, what's on your mind?
Things aren't going well with my partner... I need your help to fix our relationship.
Aw... That is not my problem.
Ah, okay. How about this grem? Do you have anything interesting to say to me?
My tummy is getting very large and I don't know why. Please come with me to the doctor.
Okay, a little inside secret... pregnant.
Okay, how about this one?
Make a contract with me, and become a magical girl!
Oh, that is not my problem either. Oh, no no no no no. I will not be doing that.
I know what happens when you sign a contract.
You should never put your name down on things.
Well, these grems were useless.
I think if I use my RPG knowledge, you're supposed to get information from NPCs... at a store!
And there's so many stalls near me!
Ah, let's go to this one.
So cute! Aw!
Are you a little worker grem? Aw...
How much do you make an hour?
Do you make enough to survive? Aw...
Oh! What is this? Mmm... For me?
Uh, that's decorative hay, not edible...
Can I ask you something?
Oh, what is this? Dialogue!
Box?
Um... Where can I get The One Ping?
Mm... Okay, yeah.
I- I can do that quest for you. Don't worry, I am the chosen one!
Ah! A ring! Wow!
I don't know what a volcano is. How is this supposed to help me save Justice?
They're gonna die! They're gonna die if a volcano erupts! Oh wait, I don't know what a volcano is.
Let's just try to find The One Ping myself.
Wait, this box looks a little suspicious.
Hmm. "Deliver to weapon shop."
Oh, cool! So another quest?
Okay!
Hey! I got a package!
I got you guys a package! It's a gift from me!
I bought this. I'll just leave it right here. Yeah!
Your BL novels?!
No, no. No. Don't- don't lose sight of the quest, Gigi.
Whoa! This is a really cool sword! I bet- I bet I could save Justice with-
Why is this so heavy for cardboard?
Oh! Oh my god!
I'm- I'm gonna put it back.
Oof! This is why- this is why Liz has so much arm strength!
Oh my god!
That sword's really cool! How much is it?
What's that? $5?!
Uh, I can't afford that.
But, uh, how about- how about I save them through the power of friendship?!
Oh, another- another text box.
Is The One Ping even real?
Okay. Sounds easy. I can do that.
W- What? I- I don't think that's how you craft an iron bar.
When did I get over here? What are these sunglasses?
Grems, this- this beat's kind of nasty! Who let you have this in the shoe shop?
Oh! Oh, okay! Okay, I'm- I'm getting it! Oh, okay! I guess- I guess we're really doing this! Haha! Okay!
Set on a quest to save my friends! I don't really know what rhymes with friends!
Old man wizard, take it from me! Evil flying birds looking for a treat!
Don't even know if he's alive or not! But who really cares with the pelmets that I got?!
Horse girls racing in my heart pacing! Got me on my knees, big skill activation!
Then a bunch of Grems surrounded me! Asked me to forge some iron bars, you see!
Wait! Wait a second! I'm starting to realize what you meant by bars!
Ha! But my rap game ate fire! And my dancing's not desired!
But if there's one thing that I'm not, it's definitely not a liar! So I hope you don't mind if I twerk up on it, you see! There's a promise that I made to Fauna!
Yeah! Oh, I'm twerking! Haha!
Ah, I don't know how to twerk! I don't want to put in the work!
You see, twerking is a skill you have to, uh, you have to train up for, everyone!
And I ran out of rhymes 30 seconds ago! All right, um...
I- I got the dance moves, and then... Okay! I can't do that!
Mic drop!
Really? You liked it?
Yippee! I got that iron bar! Yippee!
Is that- is that what I think it is? The One Ping is real! Yeah!
Oh, where's my gauntlets?
Can I have it?
Can I have one?
Oh, cool! Thanks! I'm gonna go now.
Oh, my tummy... I'm so hungry, I can't save Justice like this.
Meat?
For me?
For free?
Woah, big ass hat.
No, no, I think your hat is lovely. I love it.
Mmm, thank you. Yum, yum, yum...
Hey, by the way, I'm looking for a straw hat. Any idea where I can find one?
Oh, here we go again.
Giant rats? Where do I find one of those?
Woah, so it's a family of 26 rats?
I guess I can see why you want pictures of them. Okay.
Hey, it's picture time! I'll get pictures of all 26 of them.
Hey, yeah! Get in the frame! Let me get a picture of you.
Oh... One of them doesn't even look like a rat. That's a... that's a really big person.
What about down here?
Right, one more! One more!
That... That's a Grem!
What are you doing? You're not even a rat!
Okay, what about... what about down here?
And look at those! They look like... just like Justice!
If Justice were rats. But they're cardboard.
Woah!
Don't... don't worry. I got you. I got every angle imaginable.
That's a computer mouse.
And... and look at this photo I took. And then this one! And this one!
And this one's so cute! All these rats are so cute! And this is awesome!
And this is a yummy looking rat. Mmm, yay!
Oh! A hat! For me?! Yay!
Now I have two items!
Oh, the stables are over there.
Maybe I can get the honkshoe from the stable.
Ah! You scared me!
Bad! I'm doing bad!
It's like no one cares about me.
This cruel, evil world...
The stables!
Ah, horses! Ah, hello!
Hi! Hi there! Hey!
Oh, what do you... I can share.
Here you go, eat up!
Is... Is this horse okay?
Oh, no, I think... I think he's sleeping.
Okay, I think I can just... Don't... Don't mind if I... I'll just take this. You don't need this, do you?
I've done it! I've gathered all three items by myself! Yay!
I am the hero of this kingdom!
Sewer Grem, you probably didn't think I'd get them all, but I did! I got everything...
...because I am the hero!
Those are for you.
Oh, yay!
Oh, man. Can't believe I got everything.
Does that mean I saved Justice?
Oh, they're gonna be so proud of me.
Is there something?
No! No! Please! No, not total... Ah!
Help me!
Ow!
Why does this keep happening to me?
Where am I?
What is this?
This isn't my Fantasy Life.
A house?
Where am I going? What is...
Hey guys, what's up? How's it going, guys?
Welcome back, everyone! My name is Bae...
...and my name is Biboo!
And together we are...
BaeBoo!
Welcome back to our Let's Play!
Today we are playing a new game called...
What's it called? What's it called?
The Gimms! The Gimms!
I'm over here.
The Gimms, yeah.
It's a fresh new game off the press.
The Alpha.
We are the first ones to touch it.
So we got exclusive footage here for you today!
Let's get started!
Where are you guys taking me?
So the premise of this game... who is this character? Gigi?
What are you doing over there?
Geegi or Gigi? Probably Geegi, I don't know.
And it's kind of like a real-life simulator game.
Help!
So if I push this button right here...
...she should be able to sit down.
Let's see. Oh, there we go! What?
How'd you do that?
Ooh, the controls! Let's test them out.
Let's try a more complicated one.
Let's see if she can act like a dog.
You got that dog in you! You got that dog in you!
Of course! Only you would make me act like a dog!
Arf, arf, arf, arf!
Louder! Arf, arf, arf!
Look at the physics!
Arf, arf, arf, arf, arf!
Okay, that's enough.
So this is just the base game, right?
Guys... guys, something weird is happening!
So as of the moment, we've got the main living room...
...we've got the bedroom and the bathroom.
I think there's a kitchen attached, a kitchenette.
Where am I?
Should we go check out the kitchen?
Yeah, let's go see the kitchen!
To the kitchen!
Move into the kitchen!
I don't want to! I don't want to! Stop making me!
Let's see if there's anything we can interact with...
...in the kitchen.
My controls are broken!
Oh look, a knife! Pick up the knife!
Pick it up right now! What does she have? A knife!
Pick up a knife! Pick up a knife!
Pick it up! Pick it up!
Why is there so much input lag?
Why is the input...
Maybe the connection is just a little bit slow, it's fine.
Now put it into the stove!
Yes, into the burning hot stove!
You're selling my soul!
Do you think they accounted for this...
Ahhh!
Oh my god. Maybe that's something they can add...
...in the next update.
That was kind of anticlimactic. Oh well.
Pick up knife again!
Why? Why?
Pick up knife! Always carry a knife!
What are you guys doing to me?
All right, shall we move into another room?
Let's go into door number one! Let's see what's in there!
Walk! Walk forward! Go!
Move!
There she goes! What is in that door?
Oh, she clipped through the wall!
Okay, we got to report that bug.
Oh, there's a bathtub and there's a toilet!
I know, I know. Have you heard of Skibidi Toilet?
Oh gosh, what is Skibidi Toilet?
Alright, I'm going to make the character...
...phase into the toilet...
...and start fusing to become...
Become one with the toilet NOW!
Become one with the toilet!
Skibidi Toilet... I learn something new every day.
Skibidi dop dop dop yes yes yes...
Unhappy! Is this Skibidi Toilet? Is she happy?
Spin around! Spin your head around!
Spin my head right round, right round...
Oh, stop. I can't even fight anymore.
This is great.
If you guys like what you see, make sure you...
...like and subscribe!
Smash that subscribe button!
Wow, okay!
Don't forget to subscribe, hit that notification bell!
So you don't miss the next episode!
Yeah! There's gonna be more...
...and more! Thank you for watching! Bye!
Are they gone?
I don't hear their voices anymore.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, get me out of this toilet, I don't wanna be Skibidi Toilet.
First you take over my body, then you make me Skibidi Toilet!
How do I get out of here?
How could... how could they torture me like this?
Why do they make me do all those things?
And then they didn't even feed me!
They didn't even say that I was a good girl after they made me do all those things!
And now I'm poor!
I have to take it out on this canvas.
Ooh, if I just paint what I want, then maybe I'll be rewarded for it...
...because karma comes to good people. So...
...beautiful woman...
...boobs.
Yes! Yes! Haha!
I have done it! My greatest work yet!
My painting!
Hello?
Gigi?
Hello? Knock, knock.
Are you in there?
Okay, I'm gonna come in.
Oh, my goodness!
This absolute masterpiece!
One of the lost works of Picasso, or no... it has to be Leonardo da Vinci!
It's so incredible, I've never seen anything like it.
I can't believe that something like this is before my own eyes.
Gigi! Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, wake up!
Gigi, are you all right?
Something attacked me.
Oh, I don't know...
Why are you screaming?
Beautiful woman!
Yes, it's me. I came over just like you invited me to.
Nerissa Ravencroft?
Yes, it is I.
Is that you? And not the painting?
No, but did you make this, Gigi?
I made this.
It's incredible.
You like it?
I do. In fact...
I thought of you while making it.
Can you tell?
I can. In fact...
...if it's so that I'm your muse, maybe we could be together?
Really?
Yes, no one's ever said that to me before.
I've never wanted anything quite as much...
...after seeing this painting. The fire of my heart has been inflamed, and I feel like I cannot live without you, Gigi Murin, so...
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
Don't scream now.
Stop tickling me!
You know what? I've thought a lot of thinking...
...thought, thought about thinking, thought of it, and I've come up with a thing.
We should get married.
Oh, I thought you'd never ask!
Really? Really?
Why would you think that?
Do you want me?
I want you so bad!
You have no idea how bad I want you.
Let's go consummate our marriage!
What?
I don't know if I'm ready for that!
I don't either!
I don't know!
そう簡単な事ではないぞと
"It's not that simple," they say,
裏腹な段々と消える感触
contradicting the feeling that's fading bit by bit.
今から重なり合えるか？
Can we overlap with each other now?
静かな感情論にさようなら
Farewell to quiet emotional arguments.
ロウワー
[Title: Lower]
言いかけていた事か
Was it what I was about to say?
目惑う
Bewildered,
手探りな組み合い シーソー 墜ちるまで跨がるの？
in a blind grapple—do we ride this seesaw until we fall?
舌が痛い 苦言を吐き出さぬように込めて
My tongue aches, holding back bitter words,
骨の髄が薫りのように濁る
muddying the core of my bones like a scent.
受け止めた映画が自分さえ
Even the movie I accepted, unable to hold on,
抱え切れず手放した それを思っている
I let go of myself, still thinking about it.
荒んだ声はガラガラに 喉は焼けて唸る
My worn-out voice grows raspy, my throat burning and groaning,
何を言うべきかを分からなくて
not knowing what I ought to say.
感じてたものが遠く放たれていた
What I felt had been cast far away.
同じようで違う なんだか違う
Seemingly the same yet different, somehow different.
いつまで行こうか どこまで行けるのか
How long shall we go on? How far can we reach?
定かじゃないなら 何を想うの
If nothing is certain, what do you think?
僕らが離れるなら 僕らが迷うなら
If we drift apart, if we lose our way,
その度に何回も 繋がれるように
so that time and again, we can re-connect,
ここに居てくれないか 離れず居られたら
won't you stay here with me? If we can stay together,
まだ誰も知らない感覚 救われていく
a feeling no one yet knows will keep saving us.
えーい やっ てっ てっ てっ いや
Ei, ya te te te, iya
平穏とは素朴も思って 代わりになす
Peace is thought to be simple, acting as a substitute,
実際は格好変わりはなく
but in truth, there is no real change in appearance.
享楽とは嘘でなる
Pleasure consists of lies.
綻びの前に ここをってどこが解
Before it unravels, where is the solution?
都合の良い願いを
Convenient wishes,
同じように 同じように呟く
muttering them in the exact same way.
どこから聞こえる 何を見失うか
Where is it heard from? What will we lose sight of?
定かじゃないから 言葉は解けない
Because it's uncertain, words cannot be unravelled.
僕らが離れるなら これ以上ないなら
If we drift apart, if this is all there is,
その度に何回も 逃げ出せるように
so that time and again we can break free,
心が出会えるように
so that our hearts can meet,
奪われないように
so nothing is stolen away,
互いに目隠ししてから
after blindfolding each other,
預けていよう
let's entrust ourselves.
ナル ナル ノ
Naru naru no
ラル ラル ダ
Raru raru da
ナル ナル ノ
Naru naru no
ラル ラル ダ
Raru raru da
君と泣く
Crying with you,
君と笑う
laughing with you,
君と乞う
begging with you,
君と絶つ
severing with you,
君と乞う
begging with you,
君となす
becoming one with you.
いつまで続くだろうと
Wondering how long this will last,
同じように 同じように呟く
muttering it over and over in the exact same way.
今は忘れないよう 刻まれた空気を
So I won't forget now, this atmosphere carved into memory—
これから何度 思い出すのだろう
how many times will I recall it from now on?
僕らだけで
Just the two of us...
僕らが離れるなら 僕らが迷うなら
If we drift apart, if we lose our way,
その度に何回も 繋がれるように
so that time and again, we can re-connect,
ここに居てくれないか 離れず居られたら
won't you stay here with me? If we can stay together,
まだ誰も知らない 感覚救われていく
a feeling no one yet knows will keep saving us.
僕の言ってるすべてを
Everything I'm saying—
確かめて正しく沈め
confirm it and sink down properly.
えーい やっ てっ てっ てっ いや
Ei, ya te te te, iya
Oh, husband!
I'm so happy to be living a domestic life with you, Gigi Murin.
Well... in your awesome house, with your awesome kitchen,
and your awesome floor and this awesome couch...
Wife...
Husband!
I've never been... married before.
Me neither.
What am I supposed to do? How am I supposed to take care of you?
Take care of me? You're so sweet, no one's ever wanted to do that.
I want to take care of you. I've dreamed of this for ever...
Oh, my goodness!
...and ever! Oh, Gigi Murin!
Please, not in front of... not in front of the studio audience!
Oh, my beautiful, beautiful wife, how far do your legs go up?
As far as you want it to!
I see. That's enough.
Oh, not in front of the studio audience. Not in front of the studio audience!
I can't believe you did that.
Me?
If you say so, husband! I can't believe I'm such a dirty, dirty girl...
In front of this audience and everything? That's only for me, my dirty, dirty girl!
Yes! I wouldn't want anyone else to see me like that but you!
I should do something for you. That is what a Gigi Murin should do!
Yes! I would love that.
I should make you some toast!
Some toast for me?
Yes, for you!
You're so sweet!
Have you ever cooked before?
No, never.
Never?
Never. I don't even know how to use a microwave.
Really?
Yes, really. Yeah.
Well, I only have one thing here, and it's toast.
Wow, you're so amazing. Did you make the bread yourself, too?
I made it.
Whoa!
Oh, it's been on the floor! That's even better!
You stepped there!
Watch me... Watch me flip it, okay?
Yes, yes, I'm watching. Oh!
Watch... Watch this.
Wait, wait!
Here, wait! I have a solution. Okay.
Flip it!
Yes! You're amazing!
Ah, that made me really hungry.
Do you mind if I eat this toast first?
Of course you can. Anything for you.
Really? You're such a sweet wife.
I have to use the bathroom, my sweet.
Oh, of course.
By all means, anything you need.
If I look through the doorknob hole...
...I can see Gigi on the toilet.
Oh, Gigi... I just have to tell you...
...these last few hours together have been absolute domestic bliss.
I don't think there's any moment in my life that has been as amazing as this.
Are you still in there?
Oh, sorry!
How's the toast?
It's really good! I wish you could try some!
Oh, yeah, me too. Maybe next time.
I made this for you, so I... whatever if it was poisoned, you know?
So I had to check.
You're so thoughtful.
Well, Nerissa Ravencroft, I've been doing a lot of thinking while I was on the toilet.
Yes?
And I don't...
I don't know...
Don't say another word.
I don't know what a family entails.
I completely understand.
Will you be able to teach me?
Of course! I can teach you anything.
Really?
Of course! I'm a 10,000-year-old demon.
We can do anything you want together.
You can teach me anything?
Anything!
Anything?
Anything.
Any...
Anything your heart desires.
Well, I shouldn't keep my beautiful wife waiting.
Yes?
But I have a tummy ache.
You have a tummy ache?
Will you wait for me?
Of course! I'll wait forever for you.
Okay, hold on.
I don't think I should be eating this toast all by myself.
Don't worry.
Let me slide it under the door for you.
Oh, yeah! Okay!
Oh, wow!
How's it going?
So delicious!
Is it tasty?
It's so tasty!
Skibidi Toilet!
Never has there been bread made this amazing!
I'm glad that I made such a beautiful toast for you.
Me too!
It was my first time... Hey!
I finished it all!
All of it?
All of it, it's all in my stomach.
Was it really yummy?
So delicious.
I'm glad.
Me too.
I was really, really nervous. I still am nervous, 'cause you're so beautiful...
...and...
...I'm just a little guy on a toilet...
A little guy?
...and I have a tummy ache...
Well, don't worry.
...and there's so much wrong with me. But you're... there's everything right with you!
But that's how I feel about you!
Really?
With me, everything is wrong, but when we're together, everything is perfect!
My love, why are you crying?
No one's ever said that to me before! Wawa...
Oh, Gigi.
I'm sick and tired of these walls separating us.
Nerissa, come in here!
Let's break them down!
Sit on my lap, Nerissa.
Sit on your lap? I will!
Anything you ask for, I will do.
How about though, we move from this porcelain...
My porcelain throne?
Yeah, and we move somewhere a little more...
Okay.
...comfortable. I'm... I'm done.
Yeah?
I didn't wash my hands!
No!
Okay!
It's better this way.
Let's hold hands.
Yes, let's hold hands.
Hold my hand! Let's go to the bedroom together!
Yeah, to the bedroom!
Well, Gigi...
What's the matter?
I'm... I'm shy.
Oh, don't be shy, it's just...
I've never done this before!
You know, Gigi, the truth is, I know I said I'd teach you anything, but I've never done this before either.
Really?
Then how are we supposed to do it if you've never...
I've never done such a thing before. Who's going to teach me?
We are going to learn together.
You can just learn from nothing?
Of course.
That's so... You can just do that?
We'll find it out.
How do you think the first humans learned things, Gigi?
I don't know!
Why are you asking me that?!
Philosophical, it's pillow talk. Anyway...
Oh, oh, okay.
Well, shall we?
Well, now that you've brought it up... the first humans probably learned things by doing...
Yes!
So, let's just do it then.
Okay.
I can't wait another moment.
That was enough!
That was too much! That was way too much!
Gigi Murin, you monster.
Oh, I'm sorry! I was trying to be really gentle.
You did great.
Really?
Yes, it was amazing.
Well, I'm glad that we could spend our first day in the bedroom together as a married couple.
Yes, but Gigi, there's something strange going on.
Did you transfer your stomachache to me?
I don't think so. You can't just give a tummy ache to someone through the toes.
But it really hurts. Maybe I...
Should you use the bathroom?
I don't think so, but oh...
Gigi...
Wait a moment.
Gigi, your fingers!
No! No!
No, I'm not ready! I'm not ready!
You forgot to wear full gloves!
No!
How is it?
I can't... we can't! We don't have the money!
Gigi, I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you to get...!
This house is barely holding together!
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor!
Doctor, please! My wife, she's in pain! Can you please help?
Please doctor, please help me!
Hello? Are you gonna help her? Hello?!
Why are you laughing?
I'm giving birth here!
She is literally giving birth! And you're just laughing at her?!
Yeah...
What kind of doctor... When I go on the internet and leave bad reviews about you...
Your days are numbered! You're going out of business, and you're gonna go bankrupt!
Gigi, the baby!
Oh no!
Hold on, wait another minute!
Hold on, wait!
Gigi...
I got it!
It's safe!
Our child...
It's our baby.
It's a beautiful egg.
It is such a beautiful egg.
Wow.
We didn't need a doctor after all.
You're a natural.
You're so good at that.
It seems like we're both natural at a lot of things.
Yes, wow.
You know, I'm a little impatient. I kind of wonder...
What are you in there? Hello?
Hey.
Hello?
Are you gonna just shake the baby?
Yeah.
Wake up!
Oh my god!
It's our son!
Our son!
He is so cute!
Let's let them hold the baby.
Should we name him?
You're not gonna hold him like a mommy?
Yeah, we should name him.
Maybe we should let them name him.
Them?
Them.
Them out there?
Them out there.
Them out...
Yeah, they've been watching us this whole time, you know.
What?
Do you guys have any ideas...
They've been what?
...to name our baby?
They've been watching...
...give birth?!
They're giving name suggestions.
They're what?!
Yeah.
Those are some great suggestions, what do you think?
They're all terrible.
I'm gonna name him Neriji.
Neriji.
Yeah, cuz it's like your name and then my name, and together, and now...
It's perfect.
It's just a happy family, just you, me, Neriji, and now you're a beautiful mother, and now I'm also a beautiful father...
What else can we do?
I don't know, maybe you should go somewhere else while I take care of the baby.
Oh.
Okay.
Hush, hush hush hush hush.
Why are you still watching me? Go away!
Go away.
Better get the mail for my wife.
I think giving birth is really expensive. What if I have to pay the bills?
I don't have any money, though.
God, I hope these aren't bills.
Help! I'm drowning!
Wait, did you leave your controller on?
Oh, maybe I dropped it on the floor and...
Well, I'm not touching the controller, wait.
Wait, she's going for the ladder! Take it out! Take it out!
Yeah, take the ladder out! Take it out!
The liquid of water is filling your lungs...
The air is slowly moving out of your body as you are drowning...
Wait, she's kind of cute, though.
What's happening? Oh my god, did you see that?
Is the house on fire?
My house might be on fire now.
Whatever.
Filling your lungs with water, your soul is suffocating from the inside...
I hear the inner monologue.
Bae, help me!
I think there's a quiz function.
Oh, yeah! If your character can answer the quiz correctly, the ladder will come back as a prize!
So much water!
Are you ready for the quiz? Are you ready?
Let me out!
What is the name of the hypothetical particle that mediates the force of gravity in quantum field theory, and has not yet been observed experimentally?
A, Photon. B, Gluon. C, Graviton. Or D, Neutrino.
Answer correctly or else you will die.
It's A! It's A! I don't care, it's A!
It's A!
The answer was C, Graviton!
What do you mean?
Maybe the next character will know.
Try harder next time! Oh well.
I'm bored now.
How boring.
Oh, she died.
You took my ladder away! Help, someone help me! Mori Calliope, give me a hand! Mori Calliope, I'm drowning!
She's flashing me! While I'm dying? Mori, there's a better time for that! Stop! Stop, I can't look!
Mori Calliope! Put that away!
Hey! Hey! Listen to me. Listen to me.
I'm drowning!
Listen to me! You made me watch Dancing Fruits on TV.
You liked it!
You made me dance next to horses.
I liked that.
Fuck you.
Wait! Wait, we can talk about it! Mori Calliope, wait, what?
Die, idiot!
Mori Calliope!
So- someone help me, I'm drowning! Bae, Bae, war is killing me! They're literally drowning me! Mori Calliope, she's killing me!
I'm alive! I'm not drowning! But my wife...
My child... My beautiful wife and child, where are they? Why am I in the Grim Kingdom?
What about Nerissa? My beautiful wife! No!
Nerissa, where did you go? I love you!
Why is everything on fire? What?!
There's a dragon here?!
My friends are made out of cardboard!
They're not fire resistant! Oh no! Okay, I see the gremlins are doing their best to save them.
Okay, gremlins. What's this one doing? What are you up to?
Oh, you are not helping at all. It's okay, little gremlin. Your arms will reach one day.
These Grems on the other hand,
you have magic!
Wow!
Where'd you learn this?
Grems are so talented.
Not you, though.
It's okay.
One day...
Grems...
Grems are working really hard, so...
I, me, Gigi Murin the Hero,
is here to save the day!
Oh!
This must be my hero weapon,
as all heroes have a hero weapon.
Okay.
One million dollars?!
What?!
The kingdom can save itself.
I am not...
Oh wait! A catapult!
Of course!
Of course. Obviously.
Okay, I'll help with this.
Don't worry, Grems. Let me...
What ammo is here?
Okay.
Let's just pick this up.
Yay!
Let's go, Grem!
Let's save the kingdom!
Let's save the kingdom together!
We're barely scratching it!
I don't know what to do.
There's just no other choice.
I'm gonna have to pull out...
...that move!
Yeah! Yeah, that move!
My ultimate move!
All right, everyone.
Are you ready to see my ultimate move?
Okay.
Ikuzo!
Let's go!
Stop!
Ojisan, you scared me!
Old man, you scared me!
Wait! No!
You took the fire breath, Ojisan!
You took the fire breath, old man!
Stop it!
You're gonna die!
No! No!
No, you're getting hurt!
Please, I need you!
If you're not here, who's gonna tell me how to defeat the dragon?!
No! Don't, please! Please!
You're getting hurt!
Don't! No! No!
Are you okay?
Ojisan?
Old man?
Are you okay?
Oh no!
You saved me!
You must save...
What is it?
...this...
...kingdom...
The kingdom?
How am I supposed to save it without you?
No! Ojisan, no!
No! Old man, no!
I don't know how I'm supposed to save the kingdom...
...and destroy the dragon!
It's not taking any damage!
Get up...
Help! Call the guard
wizard graveyard
Grems come and pray, Gremdal the Grey
What the...
Danger is here, a dragons appear
What the hell?
Come seize the day, Fight and we slay
Gi gi Mu rin
Here at the scene
Look and behold, Legends Foretold
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
Where did you come from?
From near and far, hit by a car
So many of you!
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
Like... like 15 of you!
gremurin, gremurin
Wait, what are you singing about?
About me?
Help! Call the guard
Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
That's right!
I am a hero!
Come seize the day, Fight and we slay
I CAN save the day!
Gi gi Mu rin
Here at the scene
Through the power of these children singing for me...
Look and behold, Legends Foretold
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
I can do anything!
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
Yeah! Yeah, I can do it all!
She packs a punch, munch them for lunch
Okay, what should I do, Grems?
From near and far, hit by a car
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
I know! Through the power of interpretive dance!
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Joy she will bring, Grems they will sing
That's the only way we can destroy a dragon!
Nothing to fear, Gigi is here
Gremurin, come outside to pray, oh
Because it hasn't been taking physical damage!
So the best way to defeat it is through mental damage!
gremurin, gremurin
I've never done a worm before. I'm about to do a worm!
Is it working?
Help! Call the guard
Grems come and pray
Danger is here, a dragons appear
Oh, sorry, Grems! I'm sorry!
She is The Brave, souls will be saved
Please do not stare, crazy footwear
I- I'm not an interpretive dancer!
Did- Did you see here? Don't worry!
Another cartwheel! A second one even!
Yeah! And then- and then a worm!
Is it working? Is the dragon being...
...cringed out by me? Oh no, I cannot do this!
My name! You're saying my name! Is it working?
Tell me, children! Is the dragon being affected by me?
What is this? This power I'm feeling...
Oh no... It's surging in... in my veins...
Oh man... I feel it! Aaaaah yeah!
They don't call me the Fister for nothing!
That's me! The Fister!
Gigi Murin, Hololive English Justice!
I've done it!
Gigi Murin has done it!
I defeated the dragon!
I did it!
Ojisan, it was all thanks to you!
And the 15 children! But it was all thanks to you and the 15 children that I did it!
Yay!
Ojisan... Wait, you're still dead?
No! No!
I thought my power of dance could have saved you...
Ojisan, no...
Ojisan! You're okay!
The power of dance does save everyone!
You're okay, right? You're not possessed, are you?
Oh, what is this?
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, what is happening? Oh god, what's- what's happening?
What the... What the heck is happening?
Ojisan?
Ojisan! You're okay!
I've done it! Yay!
Behold, the darkness has lifted from the dragon's soul.
My final desperate strike has shattered its cruel memories!
No longer a beast of fury, it has been reborn as an innocent baby dragon!
Ahem.
にっこり調査隊 おはこんばんちは how are you?
Smiley Investigation Team! Good morning, day, and night, how are you?
今日も今日とて最高です おぉ〜わんだほい!
Today is as awesome as ever! Oh~ Wonderhoi!
What the f—
いい笑顔をつくる
Making a nice smile!
笑うのは？ だけど笑顔をつくる
Laughing? But making a smile!
はい！隊長、俺に名案が！
Yes! Commander, I have a great idea!
却下！ てかまだ何も言ってないんだが？
Rejected! But I haven't even said anything yet?!
もーとにかくあれだほら カナブンは一見にしかず？
Gosh, anyways, you know, seeing a drone beetle is believing?
あぁ 百聞は一見に如かずだねぇ
Ah, seeing is believing, right?
それそれ！
That's it, that's it!
つまり虫取り？ 違うって！
So, bug catching? No, that's wrong!
隊長！ なになに〜
Commander! What is it~
提案があります ぜひ聞かせてほしいものだな
I have a proposal. I'd love to hear it.
とりあえず とりあえず？
For now... For now?
とりあえず出発しよう ノープランで
For now, let's depart with no plan!
うん！ ちょっと待って え？
Yup! Wait a second. Huh?
出発進行！
Full steam ahead!
ちょっと待ってって！旅支度くらいさせろ〜！
Wait a second! At least let me prepare for the trip~!
気を取り直して モチベチェック始めます！
Pulling ourselves together, let's start the motivation check!
まずは基本の パ パ パ パスポート持った？
First, the basics: did you bring your pass-pass-passport?
はーい！ 着替え忘れた！ えぇっ！？
Yes! I forgot extra clothes! What!?
モ モ モバイルバッテリー持った？
Did you bring a mobile battery?
はい！ 心差しは持った？ もちろん！
Yes! Did you bring your determination? Of course!
仲間がいて 私がいて
We have friends, we have me,
しかも普通じゃない
and we're not ordinary either.
誰のことかな？
Who could you be talking about?
僕らには不可能を可能に変える何かがあるさ
We have what it takes to turn the impossible into possible!
にっこりコリコリコリコリアンダー
Smiley, crunchy, coriander!
あちらもこちらも千客万来！
Everywhere we go, endless customers!
きみの笑顔もコレクションさせて
Let me add your smile to my collection too!
YEAH!
大人も子供も関係ねえぜ
It doesn't matter if you're an adult or a kid!
これぞ一流のエンターテインメント
This is first-class entertainment!
わたしだっていつか夢を叶えてやるって We can do it!
I'll make my dream come true someday too! We can do it!
このにっこりに触れて もっと胸膨らみましたとさ！
Tasting this smile filled my heart with even more excitement!
グッド！
Good!
はい注目！
Attention, everyone!
にっこり調査隊 代々王者の仔
Smiley Survey Team, children of generational kings!
代々保つ調査の体裁
Maintaining the appearance of our survey for generations!
今だ悪を鉄拳制裁！
Now is the time to punish evil with an iron fist!
調査報告その一！
Survey Report Number 1!
エゴは全然違います！
Egos are completely different!
オバケも全然違います！
Ghosts are completely different, too!
ヤダ！めちゃ怖！
Oh no! That's super scary!
諸君！大変です！
Everyone! We have a big problem!
全然全然が足りてません！
We're completely, completely lacking everything!
とりあえず...
For now...
とりあえず... 待って じーっと見たな？
For now... Wait, you stared right at me, didn't you?
お前が言うな！
Look who's talking!
数日後
A few days later...
持ち物チェック始めまーす！
Starting the belongings check!
今夜いつものー
Tonight, as usual...
パ、パ、パスポート持った？
D-d-did you bring your passport?
はい！
Yes!
パンツ忘れた！
I forgot my underpants!
うわー！
Whoa!
モバイルバッテリー持った？
Did you bring a mobile battery?
はい！
Yes!
志は持った？
Do you have determination?
もっちろん！
Of course!
お国柄とか
Things like nationality...
老若男女は
or age and gender...
あんま関係ない！
don't really matter!
ワールドワイドだぜ！
We're worldwide, baby!
あっちも世界もまだまだすてたもんじゃないだってね！
Neither here nor the rest of the world are lost causes yet, right?
にっこりーりーりーりーお利口さん
Smiley-ley-ley-ley good kid,
陰キャも陽キャもウェルカム ウェルカム
introverts and extroverts alike, welcome, welcome!
君の笑顔が
Your smiling face...
調査対象さ！
is our survey target!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah!
メンタル doctors わけ cake
Mental doctors, sharing cake,
君の爆破のエンターテイナー
an entertainer for your explosions!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
I swear that one day I'm gonna fulfill my dreams!
We can do it!
このにっこりに触れて
Touching this smile,
もっと胸ふくらみましたとさ
my heart swelled up even more!
そのしょんぼりをにっこりに変換
Convert that sadness into smiles!
うちらのハセロメ
Our phase lock,
You, what's up?
あげの時だって
When feeling high,
さげの時だって
and when feeling low,
かき混ぜちゃって
mix it all together!
スパイスだって
Even the spices!
完璧だ！
It's perfect!
にっこりーりーりーりーお利口さん
Smiley-ley-ley-ley good kid,
大人も子供もナッツ＆サンデー
adults and children too, nuts & sundae!
もち我々も調査対象だー！
Of course, we are survey targets too!
Way way way way!
私だっていつか夢を叶えてやるって
I swear that one day I'm gonna fulfill my dreams!
We can do it!
このにっこりに触れて
Touching this smile,
もっと胸ふくらみましたとさ
my heart swelled up even more!
That's not all!
That's right! You didn't expect this!
Oh, you didn't expect this!
There's 3D MERCH! Yay!
You too! You watching at home can own your very own...
Grem Hand In Cushion! What does that mean?
Gremlin... Hand In Cushion! What does that mean?
You could put your hands in the Grem!
You can put your hands in the Gremlin!
You can remember all the good times that we had in the Grem Kingdom... Wait, Oji-san!
You can remember all the good times that we had in the Gremlin Kingdom... Wait, Ojisan!
Yay! Yay!
And you can do so many things with this Grem, like stick your hands in it, which I said!
And you can do so many things with this Gremlin, like stick your hands in it, which I said!
You can stick your hands in the Grem, and you can sleep on it, and you can squish it, and you can cherish it,
You can stick your hands in the Gremlin, and you can sleep on it, and you can squish it, and you can cherish it,
and you can love it, and it's very soft, and very squishy! Just watch Oji-san play with it! Doesn't that look cool?
3Dお披露目グッズの登場だー！ Yay!
Here comes the 3D debut merch! Yay!
見よ！このグレムのモチモチのハンドインクッションじゃよ！
Look! This is the squishy Grem Hand In Cushion!
So cute!
いっぱい可愛がっておくれよー！頼んだぞー！
Love it a lot, okay? I'm counting on you!
Yay!
Thank you everyone for coming to my 3D Live today!
I worked really, really hard on it, and thank you to the staff who was overseeing me!
And thank you for Oji-san for being here, and thank you for the Gremlins, and thank you for Calliope, and Nerissa,
and Bae, and Biboo, and Justice for being here, a part of my 3D live!
It was so much fun! Oh, it was so awesome! Thank you!
And I'm looking forward to doing more 3D things for you guys! Yay! Yippee!
And don't forget, there is MORE 3D debuts next week!
So make sure you tune in, because all of Justice has been working so hard, okay? Okay?
Bye everyone! See you later! Bye-bye!
[Grems, Thank you for being a part of my journey! It's been a crazy 1st year!]
[Sometimes it still doesn't feel real that I get to be here with you all,]
[and I'll never take this feeling for granted.]
[You are my passion! You are my strength!]
[I will keep working hard knowing that the shoebox will always be by my side.]
[I could say thank you a million times and it still wouldn't feel like enough.]
[But for all the times you've made me laugh, for the comfort you've brought me,]
[the community you've created, the joy you've shared, the stories you've crafted,]
[the whimsy that you keep alive in your heart, the shoebox that you take such good care of,]
[for always supporting me, THANK YOU <3]